MERVE TAFRALI



I am a fourth year student in the Department of Computer Engineering at Kocaeli University. In 2019, I worked as a long term trainee at Netaş. I was working in the defense department about voip and some java applications. In the summer of 2018, I did my internship in Kordsa's global IT department. I worked on c# and mvc technologies in my internship. I did an internship for 2 years as a volunteer in the school department lab. I took 3 academic publications on image processing and did the work on wordpress at Kocaeli University Laboratory of Embedded Systems.

Personal Information

Address:	Körfez/KOCAELİ
Telephone :	0545 799 48 43
E-mail:	mervetafralii@gmail.com
Gender :	Female
Birth Date:	23.12.1996
Marital Status :	Single
Nationality :	Turkish
Driving Licence:	B(2015)

Education Informations

09/2016-06/2020	Kocaeli University Faculty of Engineering Computer Engineering 2016-2020 General Percent Average:3.03/4.00
09/2010-06/2014	Derince Anatolian High School 2010-2014 General Percent Average: 68.12/100

Languages

	Writing	Reading	Speaking
English	Advanced	Advanced	Intermediate

Job Experiences

01/12/2016 -08/08/2018	Intern at Embedded System Laboratory in Kocaeli University Articles in image processing Applications in java Wordpress designer	
13/08/2018-18/09/2018	Intern at KORDSA Global It Department Supplier Management Website working with asp.net-MVC	
24/01/2019-01/06/2019	Long term intern at NETAŞ- Defense Department VolP and Java application	

Software Knowledge

C# - Advanced Python- Intermediate	6. Spring-Maven-Hibernate - Intermadiate
3. Java - Intermediate4. SQL - Intermediate5. C - Intermediate	7. Asp.net,MVC- Intermadiate8. Javascript - Beginner9. Android- Intermadiate

Projects

COURSES and CERTIFICATES

- Object Oriented Programming Java Development and Adaptation Training Elginkan - 04.03.2017 - 30.04.2017 (72 Hours)
- Computer Aided 3D Design SolidWorks Development and Adaptation Training Elginkan - 07.05.2016-25.06.2016 (60 Hours)
- Project development with Spring + Hibernate + JSP + Maven Udemy
- C # Programming Tutorial -Udemy
- American Life-English language education-up to the level c2

Social Activities

Online Games, e-Sports, Book reading, Swimming, travel, writing

Articles

- Object Detection and Segmentation on Apple Tree Images by Using Morphological Operations and Vertical and Horizontal Histogram Values
- Wound Edge Detection Operation Using Enhanced Canny Edge Detection Algorithm on Dermatological Images
- ❖ The Enhancement of Canny Edge Detection Algorithm Using Prewitt, Robert and Sobel Kernels

References

Caner İhtiyar Technology Manager in KORDSA caner.ihtiyar@kordsa.com 0505 922 09 24